The SCOAN Sunday Service
Good Morning, Church!
You may be seated; thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
There is so much blessing around.
I'm here to receive my own portion.
You know, what is good needs prayer, what is little needs prayer
and what is bad also needs prayer.
So I'm here to receive my own portion.
In Jesus' name.
[Amen!]
You are what you do, not what you say.
You are saying, "Jesus is Lord, Jesus is this" during time of confession.
But the Bible says, you are what you do, not what you say.
This shows you have to match your action with your words
because knowing facts about Jesus does not change our relationship with Him.
Tell your neighbour, "Match your action with your words".
I can't hear you.
[Match your action with your words.]
So all what you have been confessing, "Jesus is my Lord,
I will forgive my neighbour, I will do this, I will do that" -
you have to match it with your action.
When you get home, right from here, you begin to prepare your way.
When you know there is anything you have been doing in the past, before now,
it is time now to change.
This is it.
You are what you do, not what you say.
Tell your neighbour.
[You are what you do, not what you say.]
I can't hear you.
So please, it is very important.
What are you taking home to maintain your holiness?
Right now, we are ex-losers.
Right now, you are an ex-loser.
Say, right now, I'm an ex-loser!
What are you taking home to maintain your life - Christ's life of holiness?
Because you have to maintain what you have received now.
You know that immediately you leave here, it is a different thing.
You meet a lot of friends - those who divide, those who subtract.
A lot of friends.
You cannot succeed alone; you need good people.
What are you taking home to maintain what you have received?
Just think about this.
Maintenance is very important.
Ask yourself, "What am I taking home?
All what I have been seeing - to maintain the life I have received today".
You have received a new life - life without affliction,
a new life - life without failure,
a new life - life without rejection,
a new life - life without hatred,
a new life - life without tribulation.
Ask yourself, "What am I taking home to maintain this life?"
That is the question now.
I'm seeing new people, a new beginning - everyone.
But the question remains:
How will you maintain this life?
You have been very quiet.
You know the kind of life we live.
You have friends over there, people out there.
So this is what we should be thinking about, right now.
The Bible makes us to understand about genuine humility.
Before honour is humility.
We don't have enough time to talk about humility.
Humility is not to put on rags, it is not "Good Morning, sir",
beginning to greet everyone - this is what we display. No!
Before honour is humility.
Unless we are humble, we will not bow to Jesus.
Tell your neighbour, "Unless you are humble, you will not bow to Jesus".
I cannot hear you.
[Unless you are humble, you will not bow to Jesus.]
Tell your neighbour.
Unless you are humble, you will not bow to Jesus.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You say, "Ah, I'm very humble, that is why I'm in the church".
That is not the kind of humility we are talking about.
Humility will not do, hear or say without question but will ask Jesus
because Jesus is all the world to us.
Jesus is all the world to us.
Tell your neighbour, "Jesus is all the world to me".
I can't hear you.
[Jesus is all the world to me.]
Again.
That means, you have no other life.
You want to sit down, you ask Jesus, "How will I sit down?"
You want to talk, you ask Jesus, "Will I talk?"
You want to look, you ask Jesus, "Will I look? Will I greet?"
You want to dress up, you ask Jesus,
meaning you know how much you need Him.
He is all the world to me - my life, my joy, my all!
Tell your neighbour, "My life, my joy, my all!"
I can't hear you.
[My life, my joy, my all!]
Again and again.
Jesus is all the world to me.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You want to look - Jesus!
You want to sit - Jesus!
You want to greet, before you greet - Jesus!
You want to comb your hair - Jesus!
You want to eat - Jesus!
To maintain the life you have received today,
this is the procedure - Jesus must be all the world to you.
He is our strength from day to day.
He is my strength from day to day.
Say to your neighbour.
[He is my strength from day to day.]
Jesus is my strength from day to day.
Look, I want to move - Jesus!
Another leg - Jesus!
Back again - Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Tell your neighbour again.
Jesus is my strength from day to day; you don't have any other strength.
This means, the life you are living is not yours.
Oh how I love Jesus
Because He went for me
Did you listen to that?
Listen to that.
He went for you.
What manner of man is Jesus?
To maintain the life you have received now - this is a new beginning -
Jesus must be your strength from day to day.
Jesus must be your strength to maintain what you have received now.
Are you thinking about that?
For you to know that you have not been maintaining that life.
You can sit on your own - you just sit down, without relying on Him.
You just talk, you say, "Come here!"
Before you say that, "Jesus, come here!", He will guide you.
Because it is an independent mind.
I want to pray with you now.
Remember, you have received it all.
I am only just coming here to encourage you
and to make sure no one leaves here without being transformed.
Rise up for prayer.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Regardless of what you are going through - take note of that.
Regardless of what you are going through.
Say, "Regardless of what I am going through in the natural".
You can be having a headache now.
But above, over there, the headache is gone.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Take note of that. I want you to understand it before I offer my prayer to you.
You must know this.
Regardless of what you are going through in the natural.
It means, you can be in trouble now.
Not in the natural but over there, above, there is no trouble.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
"Ah, I don't know why this is happening to me."
But you don't know whether what is happening to you is still happening to you in the spirit.
If what is happening to you now is not happening to you in the spirit,
definitely, you are blaspheming.
Someone is working out the answer -
what God is working out for you now.
Regardless of what you are going through in the natural -
it may be painful in the natural, it may be rough in the natural -
Jesus says, "The way out for you has come!"
Are you taking my word?
By the time you leave here - you will leave here today, tomorrow or any other day -
you will say, "Yes"; you will send me an email, "You have said it T.B. Joshua".
Why can't you begin to rejoice?
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Yes.
You have been praying to play football.
But you have not played football.
But we are telling you, "This is the outcome of the game";
that you are a winner.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
The way out for you...
[...has come.]
I want you to finish the word.
[The way out for me has come.]
The way out for your business has come!
The way out for your health has come!
The way out for your marriage, career has come!
What else, if I'm telling you.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
If you are praying to God, "Lord, please, this man promised to borrow me millions of dollars",
and you prayed that the Lord should touch his heart and you have been praying since morning,
will the man come inside the church to give you the loan?
And I'm telling you now that when you get home, the man is waiting to give you a loan.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
So this is just the picture of what I'm painting.
Concerning your health, that pain - you feel that pain.
You are telling me something in the natural and I'm telling you something in the spirit.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I can see God's deliverance touching you!
I can see God's deliverance touching your finances!
I can see God's deliverance touching your finances, in the name of Jesus Christ!
I am not coming here to pray; I am here to prophesy.
What I have seen in the spirit is what I am telling you now.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Tell your neighbour, "Be patient and wait for the physical manifestation now!"
Take note of 'now'! I'm not saying just be patient; wait for the physical manifestation now!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
This year, 1st January, the Lord said, "Go to the mountain. Meet me somewhere".
I said, "Which mountain?"
The Lord said, "A quiet place.
A place where when I'm praying, I will not be able to close my eyes because of fear.
Tiger can come this way, lion may come this way,
python may come this way. Inside the thick forest".
Where I will not be able to close my eyes.
You yourself - it is your idea and culture that when you want to pray...
If I carry you to where I went to last January - ah!
Even you would not want to pray louder because you don't know what is coming out.
When I got there, the second day, the Lord said to me, "This year is very fearful".
"This year is a very fearful year?"
"I'm bringing you here to pray for your nation and for the whole world at large and for your people."
"How will I offer the prayer?"
"Stay here for three days. I will give you a word to say."
I am just telling you what is in the spirit.
If care is not taken - proper care - it may hang for years.
Do you know that many are here that are not supposed to be a follower,
are supposed to be a leader and their leadership has been released in the spirit
but yet, they are still a follower.
Something can be hung for many years in the spirit
which is no longer in the hands of God.
God will release - "Ok, this thing is for Mr T.B. Joshua."
And it will continue rolling and rolling in the spirit there.
And yet, for years, T.B. Joshua has not yet received it.
And you will continue to pray to God, "God, give me bread, give me bread",
whereas that bread has been released over there.
But the bread you were to have received instantly is just there
because what you do is different from what you say.
So the thing will just be there.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Sometimes, when I see people on the street and I look at them,
"This man is not supposed to be on the street.
He is supposed to be in the palace.
Ah, this man is supposed to be in the palace but he is on the street".
Sometimes I see people lamenting, crying
whereas when I look at the person that is crying and lamenting,
this is a crown; somebody who is supposed to wear a crown.
One of the best men in the world is now on the street - one of worst men in the world.
On the last day, you will now find out, "This is the life I lived. This is the life God designed for me".
Tell your neighbour, "I am what I do, not what I say".
I can't hear you.
[I am what I do, not what I say.]
I am what I do, not what I say.
Match your actions with your words.
That is why when we say, "In Jesus' name", we are talking to the air.
If you are what you say, anytime you say, "In Jesus' name",
Jesus will come to the scene.
But many times you say, "In Jesus' name", Jesus does not come to the scene
because you are what you do
Think about that.
Knowing facts about Jesus does not change your relationship with Him.
Tell your neighbour, "Knowing facts about Jesus does not change my relationship with Jesus".
Listen to me.
I can see God's deliverance touching you - touching your life, touching your career.
Somebody touched me
Somebody touched my soul
While I was praying
Praying to my Father
Somebody touched my soul
Somebody touched me
While I was praying
Praying to my Father
Somebody touched my soul
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
It must be Jesus
Jesus Christ touched my soul
While I was praying
Praying to my Father
Jesus Christ touched my soul
I can see God's healing touching you, in the name of Jesus!
I am telling you what I am seeing in the spirit.
Allow it to happen.
I can see God's healing touching your life!
Allow it to happen, in the name of Jesus!
Tell your neighbour, "Be patient and wait for the physical manifestation now, in the name of Jesus!"
Recount again.
I can see God's deliverance touching your life.
I recount again.
I can see God's deliverance touching your business.
I can see God's deliverance touching your marriage, in the name of Jesus!
The way out for you has come!
I can't hear you.
[Amen!]
Say to yourself, "The way out for me has come!"
I can't hear you.
[The way out for me has come!]
The way out for your career has come!
The way out for my career has come!
The way out for my business has come!
The way out for my good health has come!
The way out for my marriage has come, in Jesus' name!
Rejoice!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
This is my message to you.
You should allow it to happen.
You have a role to play to allow it to happen.
Don't forget.
Don't harbour unforgiving spirit; don't harbour grudges.
Holding offence grieves the Holy Spirit.
Thank You, Lord!
In Jesus' name.
Lift up your voice and let us pray for your nation.
Whatever you have as a contact, contact point, let us pray for your nation.
God's intervention!
God's intervention, in Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I can't hear you.
[Amen!]
Thank You, Lord!
Let us pray for nations that are not at peace because of war, crises.
Wherever that nation is - all over the world - send your prayer of peace.
Lift up your voice and pray.
Ask God to rain the rain of peace, rain of harmony on nations.
Wherever - East, South, North continent, South Continent.
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Let us pray for your journey.
Your journey of righteousness is not yet over.
You need to live the rest of your life to maintain your holiness.
Jesus will come like a thief in the night - no one knows when and how.
Therefore, you have to be alert, be conscious of what you do and what you say.
"Ah, am I saying what God wants me to say?"
"Am I doing what God wants me to do?"
Don't go where Jesus is not invited.
Be conscious of what you do, what you say.
Prayer.
Ask God to strengthen you.
Ask for the grace of God to cover to you, His strength from day to day,
in Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I can't hear you.
[Amen!]
Hallelujah.
God's intervention.
Right now, I pray you become God's channel from today -
a channel of light where there is darkness,
a channel of love where there is hate,
a channel of faithfulness where there is unfaithfulness,
a channel of obedience where there is disobedience,
a channel of humility where there is pride, in Jesus Christ's name.
I can't hear you.
[Amen!]
Thank You, Lord.
TT: Mel Flowers 01/05/2019